## Jinyeong Seo

#### Overview

I am a Ph.D. student at Seoul National University, advised by Prof. Yongsoo Song. My research interest lies in (but is not limited to) the practical instantiation of cryptographic protocols using techniques from lattice-based cryptography. Specifically, my recent research focuses on improving the performance of lattice-based proof systems and homomorphic encryption schemes. I also have broad interests in the theoretical foundations of cryptographic proofs.

### Education

## **Seoul National University**

Seoul, South Korea

**Ph.D.** in Computer Science

Mar. 2022 – Present

Advisor: Prof. Yongsoo Song

### **KAIST**

Daejeon, South Korea

**B.S.** in Mathematical Science

Mar. 2016 – Aug. 2021

(double major: computer science)

### **Publications**

Authors are listed in alphabetical order by last name, unless an asterisk (\*) is indicated.

### Conferences

## [C07] Simpler and faster BFV Bootstrapping for Arbitrary Plaintext Modulus from CKKS

Jaehyung Kim, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song

ACM CCS 2024

# [C06] Concretely Efficient Lattice-based Polynomial Commitment from Standard Assumptions

Intak Hwang, Jinyeong Seo, Yongsoo Song.

CRYPTO 2024

# [C05] Optimizing HE operations via Level-aware Key-switching Framework

Intak Hwang, Jinyeong Seo, Yongsoo Song.

WAHC 2023

# [C04] Asymptotically faster multi-key homomorphic encryption from homomorphic gadget decomposition

Taechan Kim, Hyesun Kwak, Dongwon Lee, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *ACM CCS 2023* 

## [C03] Toward Practical Lattice-based Proof of Knowledge from Hint-MLWE

Duhyeong Kim, Dongwon Lee, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *CRYPTO 2023* 

[C02] Accelerating HE Operations from Key Decomposition Technique Miran Kim, Dongwon Lee, Jinyeong Seo, Yongsoo Song.

CRYPTO 2023

## [C01] Faster TFHE Bootstrapping with Block Binary Keys

Changmin Lee, Seonhong Min, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yongsoo Song. *ACM ASIACCS 2023* 

Journals

# [J01] \*HEaaN-STAT: a privacy-preserving statistical analysis toolkit for large-scale numerical, ordinal, and categorical data

Younho Lee, <u>Jinyeong Seo</u>, Yujin Nam, Jiseok Chae, Jung Hee Cheon *IEEE TDSC 2023* 

Experiences

### CryptoLab Inc.

Seoul, South Korea

- Researcher

Sep. 2019 - Mar. 2020

- Intern

Jun. 2019 – Aug. 2019

- Developed HEaaN-STAT, homomorphic encryption-based statistical analysis toolkit.

eWBM Inc.

Seoul, South Korea

- Intern

Jun. 2018 - Aug. 2018

- Developed ECDH PKI protocols for secure communication on LoRa devices.

Presentations

## Simpler and faster BFV Bootstrapping for Arbitrary Plaintext Modulus from CKKS Oct. 2024

ACM CCS 2024

Concretely Efficient Lattice-based Polynomial Commitment from Standard Assumptions

Aug. 2024

CRYPTO 2024

# Practical Lattice-based Private Stream Aggregation and Application to Federated Learning Aug. 2023

The 5th Privacy-Preserving Machine Learning Workshop 2023

Honors & Awards

### **Student Travel Grants**

Oct. 2024

Travel Grant (\$750)

ACM CCS 2024

### **Korea Cryptography Contest**

Oct. 2023

Top Award (\$10, 000)

National Security Research Institute

## 29th Samsung Humantech Paper Award

Silver Award (\$7, 000)

**Samsung Electronics** 

**Korea Cryptography Contest** 

Oct. 2022

Feb. 2023

Excellence Award (\$2,000)

National Security Research Institute

GitHub Repositories

https://github.com/SNUCP/level-aware-ksw PoC Implementation of [C05] https://github.com/SNUCP/snu-mghe PoC Implementation of [C04] https://github.com/SNUCP/fast-ksw PoC Implementation of [C02] https://github.com/SNUCP/blockkey-tfhe PoC Implementation of [C01]

Skills

**Programming**: C, C++, Go, Python